[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Oscar for Best Actress in a Supporting Role at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "Angelina Jolie", "incorrect_answers": ["Helen Hunt", "Jennifer Garner", "Anne Heche"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Operation Petticoat who portrayed Lt. (j.g.) Nicholas Holden?", "correct_answer": "Tony Curtis", "incorrect_answers": ["Cary Grant", "Dick Sargent", "Gavin MacLeod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor directed and starred in the popular 1990 movie Dances with Wolves?", "correct_answer": "Kevin Costner", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Connery", "Mel Gibson", "Harrison Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of celestial body is the 9949 Brontosaurus?", "correct_answer": "Asteroid", "incorrect_answers": ["Planet", "Star", "Black hole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cheetahs have been domesticated and tamed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What leavening agent is used for the popular French bread called Baguette?", "correct_answer": "Yeast", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Baking powder", "Baking soda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many nucleotides of DNA does it take to encode a single amino acid in a given protein?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "25", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What types of food should not be mixed, consumed or stored together according to Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "Meat and dairy products", "incorrect_answers": ["Dairy products and vegetables", "Meat and fish", "Eggs and rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the British post-apocalyptic horror movie 28 Days Later, the virus that causes people to become violent zombies is started by what kind of animals?", "correct_answer": "Chimpanzees", "incorrect_answers": ["Wolves", "Cats", "Bats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Roman numerals, what is the symbol for 1000?", "correct_answer": "M", "incorrect_answers": ["L", "C", "D"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did French mechanic Nicolas Joseph Cugnot invent the first self-propelled road vehicle?", "correct_answer": "1769", "incorrect_answers": ["1891", "1824", "7874"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grasslands cover this part of land on Earth.", "correct_answer": "1/5th", "incorrect_answers": ["1/2th", "1/17th", "1/10th"]}]